SAMUEL TROY DOMINGUEZ

Smart Contract Auditor / Security Researcher

+1-737-219-917El Paso, TX

@ samueltroydomi@gmail.com

https://www.github.com/samtdomi

SUMMARY

Smart Contract Auditor specializing in Solidity, with the ability to apply advanced knowledge of smart contract development to the business logic within a protocol's codebase in order to find vulnerabilities, write code to solve the vulnerabilities, and communicate the findings to the developers to further secure the protocol and web3.

EXPERIENCE

Competitive Smart Contract Auditing

CodeHawks

苗 2023 - Present 👂 El Paso , Texas

Auditor on CodeHawks completing over 12 professional audits, documenting over 70+ findings on projects paying rewards up to \$75,000 (disbersed to auditors submitting findings).

- 15 High Severity Findings
- · 14 Medium Severity Findings
- 25+ Low / Gas Findings

Smart Contract Auditing

Independent Auditing

苗 2023 - Present 👂 El Paso , Texas

25 Flesellt V Li Faso, lexas

Audited 3 independent protocols to completion, for free, generating a complete audit report for each.

- Audited Over 4,000 nSloc
- · Fully Completed PDF Audit Report
- · Created Stateful Fuzz Test Suite
- · Created Stateless Fuzz Test Suite
- Invariant Testing
- Foundry
- Hardhat

TRAINING / COURSES

FreeCodeCamp: Blockchain, Solidity, and Full Stack Web3 Development with Javascript (32 hour course)

Cyfrin: Smart Contract Security and Auditing (24 hour course)

Cyfrin / Chainlink: Foundry 101 (10 hour course)

Cyfrin / Chainlink: Advanced Foundry (13 hour course)

SKILLS

Solidity	Smart Contracts		DeFi
Foundry	Hardhat	Slither	·
Ethereum	JavaScrip	ot Py	rthon
Consenus	Algorithms		
Distributed Systems		Data S	tructures

Chainlink

STRENGTHS

Blockchain



Collaboration

Adaptable to work within a team and Execute my role for the benefit of the objective of the team.



Self Starter / Self Accountability

I am my biggest critic and hold myself accountable to goals and tasks. I am selfmotivated and discipline.



Attention to Detail

Always pay strict attention to details because even an unimportant error could lead to missing a vulnerability that can cause the protocol to lose unprecedented amounts and cause harm to the users.

INDUSTRY EXPERTISE

INDUSTRIENPERIISE				
DeFi Protocols				
Solidity				
Smart Contract Development				

EDUCATION

Bachelors of Science, Finance

University of Texas at El Paso

= 2017 - 2020